# Shan Yang

Computer Science Department UNC at Chapel Hill NC, United States

Email: alexyang@cs.unc.edu

Phone: 732-421-3483

Website: http://cs.unc.edu/~alexyang

## **PROFILE**

I currently work as a research assistant for Prof. Ming C. Lin in GAMMA group. My research interest is mainly on inverse problems in computer graphics and computer vision. It involves optimization, numerical PDE/ODE solving and machine learning.

## RESEARCH AND WORK EXPERIENCE

- Research Assistant, with Prof. Ming C. Lin, UNC Chapel Hill 2013.01-Present Worked on elasticity parameter recovering project
- Summer Intern, Research, Google 2016.05-2016.08 Worked with Chris Bregler and Bryan Seybold on computer vision and VR related topics
- Summer Intern, Advanced Processor Lab, Samsung Research America 2014.05-2014.08 Worked with Liangiun Zhang on design and implement a test framework
- Summer Intern, Advanced Processor Lab, Samsung Research America 2013.05-2013.08 Worked with Magnus Edman on CPU usage visualization
- Research Assistant, with Prof. Leonard McMillan, UNC Chapel Hill 2012.08-2012.12 Worked on tubule recognition and classification in microscopic testis images

#### **EDUCATION**

- University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill, NC, United States 2012-present
- Shanghai Jiao Tong University, Shanghai, China BE, 2012

Overall GPA: 90.3 / 100 (3.82/4.0) Rank: Top 5 among 137 students

#### HONORS AND AWARDS

- China Aerospace Science and Technology Corp. Scholarship, top 5% students
- Tung OOCL Scholarship, top 5% students
- Excellent Bachelor Thesis of Shanghai Jiao Tong University, top 1% students

#### **PUBLICATIONS**

- Shan Yang, Tanya Amert, Zherong Pan, Ke Wang, Licheng Yu, Tamara Berg, Ming C. Lin, "Detailed Garment Recovery from a Single-View Image", ACM Transaction on Graphics (TOG), 2016 (accepted)
- Lichens Yu, Patric Poirson, Shan Yang, Alex Berg, Tamara Berg, "Modeling Context in Referring Expressions", European Conference on Computer Vision (ECCV), spotlight, 2016
- Shan Yang, Vladimir Jojic, Jun Lian, Ronald Chen, Hongtu Zhu and Ming C. Lin, "Classification of Prostate Cancer Grades and T-Stages based on Tissue Elasticity Using Medical Image Analysis", International Conference on Medical Image Computing and Computer Assisted Intervention (MICCAI), 2016

- **Shan Yang**, Ming C. Lin, "Bayesian Estimation of Non-Rigid Mechanical Parameters Using Temporal Sequences of Deformation Samples", IEEE International Conference on Robotics and Automation (ICRA), 2016
- **Shan Yang**, Ming C. Lin, "Material Cloning: Acquiring Elasticity Parameters from Images", IEEE Transactions on Visualization and Graphics (TVCG), 2016
- **Shan Yang**, Ming C. Lin, "Simultaneous Estimation of Elasticity for Multiple Deformable Bodies", Journal Computer Animation and Virtual Worlds (CAVW), 2015
- **Shan Yang**, Wenlong Lu, Lixu Gu, "Real time simulation for buried suture", Computer Assisted Radiology and Surgery (CARS), 2012

### **SKILLS**

- Programming: C++, C, Python, Java
- Scientific Computing